oh
[Music]
you want cheese on it yes
any preference
sorry any preference
just normal burger cheese
mexican or edmonton
no no
okay
[Music]
good
you're gonna sit down here and eat it or
we're gonna take it away please
when you eat up here
so
[Music]
uh just onion tomato
any sauce
um
i'll just catch up
[Music]
okay
yeah please
play no spicy like
[Music]
you have any preference to the cheese
i've got four different kind of cheese
what you've got spicy cheese a little
spicy i've got a manta i've got blue
cheese i've got three
spicier yeah
sold out
you can have a problem
um
[Music]
sat down
any preference for the cheese
what's your choice about cheese egg
somewhere
mexico
oh
[Music]
people
thank you
[Music]
yeah that's it
getting away
thank you
um
[Music]
oh
any preference with the cheese
it is yes
[Music]
all right
any sauce
[Music]
foreign
as well
[Music]
oh
right
just a few chicks
okay
[Music]
you're gonna
um
anything else
futures
enjoy cheers
yes
is
[Music]
um
any
i'll never
that's a good thing
[Music]
oh
kieran
i
one day you're going to surprise me
never
oh yeah how was it
[Music]
just onion and
um
[Music]
any preference in the cheese
four different kind of cheese and stuff
that's gonna burger cheese
[Music]
just on your
hey
ruler
again
[Music]
any preference for the cheese
sure i've got four different kind of
shoes today
[Music]
yes
any preference
[Music]
more speed on it
okay
[Music]
can i move
switch in here
eating take away
or anything else
oh
[Music]
uh
any sauce
let's have a bit more
[Music]
yes
ordinary cheese here
[Music]
yes
you know
shoes
amazing
[Music]
um
you at the park
we don't know how much is it
[Music]
any sauce
it's just
um
[Music]
and how do you have a little bit of
cancel
anything else just a little bit
any sauce
[Music]
um
can i have necklace cucumber
very tasty
um
just a bit of ketchup please
[Music]
good night
it would have been